All right, y'all. We are live on this
beautiful Wednesday, Tuesday. Tuesday.
Is it a Tuesday afternoon? God bless
everybody. In the name of Yeshua, Jesus
the Messiah. I do pray you and your
family are blessed as Bitcoin is taking
a dump, man. We are taking a dump. My
goodness. And yeah, I'm trying to catch
a knife, guys. I'm trying to catch a
knife right here. Oh my goodness. I'm
freaking out. I'm legitimately freaking
out right now as I'm trying to catch
this knife, man. You know, I'm not going
to lie. I'm not going to lie. All right.
Yesterday, you know, we were long from
here yesterday. That trade ended up
going pretty well actually. We ended up
coming up here. You know, I let everyone
know that I took the trade yesterday and
this morning I I let everyone know that
I hit a TP at the VWOP.
We came up to 64360.
That's where I hit the TP.
And it's a good thing because from that
exact point, which was right here, we
got to move back to the downside. Now,
that trade did get closed out for a
small profit.
But you know what? We're going for it
again. And honestly, it's not looking
the best. It's really not looking the
best right now. The question is, am I
about to get absolutely sliced, diced,
wrecked, and destroyed on this long
trade, this juicy knife catch long trade
from the exact bottom setup given in
advance
in the moment in the Casper Crew VIP
Discord? Well, time will tell as it is
currently 2:00 p.m. And tomorrow, guys,
let's not forget what's coming tomorrow.
Tomorrow is CPI, baby.
CPI. What day is it? What What month is
it? It's August 12th. Core CPI coming
out tomorrow. And people are expecting
inflation to go down. Maybe the market's
waiting for tomorrow to give us a big
move, but honestly,
we will have to wait and see. Big shout
out to everybody in the chat right now
as we are holding this trade as we are
losing money out the wazoo. I have a
$400,000 position open Bitcoin long
trade from the exact bottom here.
[laughter]
Oh my goodness. Big shout out to
everybody in the chat. Spank Mapleton.
Tomorrow they lie about inflation. Shout
out to Valerie Valenuela. Aloha Jason.
God bless you and your family. God bless
you as well. Shout out to R Pink. Shout
out to Sudi. Shout out to Splashfire
Films holding it down with the wrench.
Shout out to Travy Trades and good old
Chain. Wait, hang on. Hang on. I'm going
to try and pronounce this one.
Chaitanany
Al Mashankar
109. IHV short.
You have a short. Okay, cool, man. Okay,
cool. Let's see what happens. I have a
long. All right. All right. Big shout
out to the369
who says, "I don't think so, bro. He is
too smart for that BS."
He's talking to Magga Cherry. Shout out
to Crypto Crank. He says, "Ola, we are
long at the same GP entry." All right,
bro. Crypto Crank probably already took
profit. He probably made like $70,000 on
this move. Jake Jay Hasp is about to
round trip. About to round trip it,
baby. [laughter and gasps] Oh my
goodness.
Uh, big shout out to Persit Sharma.
Shout out to Magga Cherry. Jay is a
spherical earther. People in the chat,
they're calling me a spherical earther.
People are calling me a flat-earther.
People are out here slandering Jason
Casper left and right calling me
spherical flat earth. All these
different earth shapers. What earth
shaper are you? Do you believe in a
triangly a triangularly shaped earth? A
pyramid-shaped earth? Big shout out to
Not Quicker. Is the Alpha Rooster in the
trading room or on his mom's garage? The
Alpha Rooster,
as you can see, is in the office.
The expensive office with the real neon
lights, the real trading monitors that I
spent tens of thousands of dollars on
just to try and one up Crypto Lifer.
Big shout out to Chef Money. Big shout
out to Make Me a Millie. Big shout out
to Cryptogian.
Shout out to Summit Trade Signals.
What's What's happening? What's
happening, bro? What's happening? What's
happening? Big shout out to aa fog long.
Yeah, I'm in a long, man. So, let's see
what happens. Let's see what happens,
man. I've got this stop loss set here.
63 250. 63250. Let's see. We're We're
forming this disgusting looking range
here. Man, I have to be honest. I'm
shaking in my boots right now. And the
irony is I'm not even wearing boots, but
I mean we are forming this bearish
looking wedge right now. Man, this looks
like we just want to go for the
liquidity
frame.
We're going to talk about why I took it
long from here, guys. And and all the
stuff. All right, don't worry. We're
going to talk about all the stuff that
you guys are dying to know about. All
right, all the stuff that we're dying to
know about. Why don't you have your
entry between the 618 and 76? This is
the 618, man. I don't know what what
else what else to say.
Uh,
I don't know what else to say.
Earth is a plane of existence. It's not
flat or round because it doesn't
actually exist. Quantum mechanics proves
this. I kind of lean that way, bro. I
kind of lean that way. I kind of lean
towards Earth is just a realm. It's a
realm. Earth is a realm. No one asks
like, "What shape is heaven? What shape
is hell? What shape is shol? What shape
is Hades? What shape is Tardris?" No one
asked that because we understand they're
just realms of existence.
You know what I'm saying? That's kind of
where I'm at, honestly.
Yo, that turtle. This is interesting,
says Magax Cherry.
Shout out to Learn Repy.
He says, "Smash the likes."
Shout out to Cryptocowpoke. It's Texas
shaped. We call it the fivepoint messa.
All right. Not sure what that means.
Travy trades believes in in in an oblate
spheroid earth. That's cool, man. Yes,
that's right. Stakes sauce. We're in the
office, baby. Mom's garage is done. All
right. You can tell I've got a new
hairstyle.
Look at how fresh
your boy Jay Casp is looking today.
We got a new style. We got a new office.
Things are looking up, guys. The Bitcoin
price is even pumping right now. We're
getting one big blue candle over here on
Antarctic Exchange. You know what I'm
saying? Um,
put the hat back on. [music] Big shout
out to the Casper crew, uneven butt
chick,
shaped earth, Alpha Rooster, and Mom's
Garage. All right, let's pop on. Let's
pop on to the actual chart.
You know what I'm saying? Shout out to
Travy Trades. Travy Trades with the with
the with the nice looking logo, man.
He's got some big things in the works.
Got some big things in the works.
All right. All right. Let's go, baby.
Let's pop right in to the Bitcoin chart.
Are we ready? Boom. Here we go, guys.
All right. Let's clear off the chart.
I'm so excited to talk about Bitcoin.
You guys have no idea. So, we're going
to go to the 1 hour chart here. And
here's the here's the thing that stands
out to me. Someone said 1 hour butt
chicks on the on the chart here. And I
do have to say, guys, the one thing that
really does stand out to me right now is
this. Bam. All right. As the price is
getting lower like this,
the the the oscillator is getting
higher. Like, price is getting lower,
oscillator's getting higher. Dolores has
the coffee. She's coming out to the
table. She's got the caffeinated
beverage in her hand.
And it's making me feel something, guys.
It's making me feel something. We go to
the 24-minute chart and what do we see?
Oh my goodness. Money flow getting
higher. Purple into the blue. What she
do? We got the bit boy butt cheek on the
24m minute. My goodness golly gosh. Put
me on a tractor and call me Aunt Sally.
It's looking like maybe we could get a
move. It's looking like maybe we could
get a move on the on the on the
24-minut. We go to the 12minut. What do
we see? Well, things looking a little
bit less awesome on the 12, but I do
have to say the money flow is loyal. All
right, the money flow is definitely
loyal on the 12. And at the very least,
maybe we get one more drive to the
downside, but it is looking bottomy
here. Even on the 12, we got the money
flow coming up like the coffee and the
cup, the six minute. Same deal. money
flow on the six-minute loyal divergences
eh
you know divergences eh but but to be
fair but to be fair we do have some
divergences even on the six-minute now
the six-minute money flow is starting to
look shady coming back down to the
bottom so why am I looking for longs at
this area why am I long right now why do
I have $400 of my hard-earned cash that
I had to go to McDonald's and flip
hamburger patties for decades just to
earn on a trade right now like What?
What? What would what would make me take
a trade here? I'll tell you guys exactly
what it is. We take a Fibonacci from the
low to the high. Oh my goodness. Would
you look at this? We are getting a
bounce right now from the Fibonacci
golden pocket. Amazing. What a beautiful
level that is right from the pocket.
We're getting a little bit of a bounce
from the pocket. Can you even spot it?
But not only are we getting a bounce
from the pocket, we take a look at the
weekly chart. And what else do we notice
about this golden pocket? Is there
anything else we can see here? Any other
confluences that we can squeeze into the
cup of orange juice? Why yes, I do see
another confluence, which is this this
weekly order block right here with the
candle closes and opens, right? It's
going to be a key level right there. A
double bounce from that level. Even if
we go to the daily time frame, we can
see that we have a a daily order block
right here as well with the candle body
open and close. We got this triple juice
right here. confluence amazing on the
chart like a beautiful work of art as
we're coming down getting a bounce from
the double zone of of liquidity here and
and and that is why I'm I'm looking for
a long here now does this mean we're
absolutely going to bounce from this
zone well here's the thing guys I'll be
honest and I you know look
the answer is no I I honestly don't know
if we're going to bounce from here but
the way I trade is when I see a setup
with divergences I have to take it I
have to take it with good risk
management because if I don't take it
with good risk management and then we
pump forever, then I say, "Why didn't I
take the trade? I had my confirmations."
If I take the trade and I had
confirmations and I take a loss, guess
what? I'm okay with that. I'm okay with
that. Look, I had confirmations. We're
at a level. I took a trade. It was a
loss. No big deal.
But if I see a trade come and I don't
take it and then we pump, then I hate I
I don't want to say I hate myself cuz,
you know, that's some strong language.
But I'm very upset with myself for not
following through. Now here is the one
thing that gives me c caution caution.
We have to be cautious.
The reason we need to be cautious here
is because if we take a look at the
chart, it's quite clear that we've
rejected from the value area high. We've
rejected once again from the point of
control. And so the the highest
probability is that we will make our way
down to the 786 plus the value area low,
which is right around $63,000.
even.
And so if we don't hold this level,
honestly, it probably we're coming down
lower. You know what? We might even come
down lower. We might get a little bit of
a bounce here and make a lower high and
then boom, come back back down even
lower. All right, that is the the
different kind of scenarios that we are
looking for right now.
But we are still holding the long.
We got a little bit of money. 600.
Somehow the funding fee paid me bank.
Wow. Would you look at that funding fee
on this already? Cheese.
Cheese. Swiss cheese and cheddar. Swiss
cheese and cheddar.
So again guys, remember this is really
the zone that Bitcoin needs to hold if
we want to see a breakout toward the
mid70s. And if we lose this green box of
hope and wonder at $63,000, then I have
to flip totally bearish. All right.
You're going to see the thumbnails
change here. You know, we're going to
just I'll I'll show you a little trick
here that Jason Casper can do in the
flip of a candle. Watch this. Boom. Wow.
You see what I'm saying here? You see
what Oh, watch this. I could even put a
little bit of this action on here. Oh,
yeah. Look at that. O, looking bearish.
And we we stretched that purple candle
out big, man. Oh my goodness. I'm ready
for it. I'm Oh, watch this.
Oh my goodness. Wow. Oh yeah, this I
mean look, I'm already ready for it,
man. I'm about to flip bearish if we
lose that box. I've already got the
thumbnail right here. Get a little bit
of Bitcoin action on there. I mean, it
is it is just sensational. My goodness.
You know what I'm saying? I've got it
all ready to go because if we lose this
green box, then guess what? Then I say
we're coming down to this zone right
here, $60,000ish dollars. All right. And
again, we've labeled this on the chart,
but this one here, this is what I call
the bygon. All right, it's called the
bygon. This is the bygon setup, right?
The by gone. All right,
the bygon setup, right? Why is it called
the bygon setup? Because, guys, this
really is the big one. All right, as you
can see from your screen here, this is
the big one.
All right. But we don't we don't we we
we we we do a little bit different here.
We pronounce it bygon in the in the in
the Casper crew. This is the bygon.
All right. As you can see right here,
spelled the same way. Big one. Bygon.
But this could be a big swing trade
here. And I'll tell you why. I'm not
going to lose my bullish bias here given
the context of the higher term time
frames such as the weekly confirmed
bullish divergence.
As you can see the daily trigger wave.
This is giving us this this this red
wave on the daily here. Yes, this could
take us down. But in overall context of
this, this looks more bullish than
bearish to me. This looks like we get a
little bit of a retrace and then bounce.
So either that retrace is coming right
here to the small one or we're coming
down to the bygon. If we come down to
the bygon
man this could be this could be like I
said this could be the bygon because
again we would have something like this.
We would have a nice bullish divergence.
We would have a nice continuation
trigger wave from a very key support
which we didn't have with this trigger
wave. And that could take us back to the
top of the range around 67 $68,000.
Right? That is really what I'm looking
for next. If we can't hold the small
one, then we come down to the bygon. But
right now, we are bouncing from the top
level of the small one. We're going to
go to the one hour and see how she's
looking here. Again,
the question here on everyone's mind is,
are we going to confirm a green diddly
doot dot on the 1 hour market cipher B?
All right. Are we going to confirm a
green diddly doot dot on the 1 hour
market cipher B? That is the question.
We've already confirmed a green diddly
dot in the 24-minute money flow getting
higher. We got the green diddly dots
coming in just to hit the spot.
Hopefully we don't get shot and we come
back down. You know what I mean?
Yeah. We got the green diddly duke dot
coming in, [music] baby. Just to hit the
spot. Hopefully our trade doesn't get
shot cuz we were so right, we start to
rot. We got the green diddly doot dot.
24 minutes Bitcoin high iron cuz she
eats her spinach. Just kidding. She's a
carnivore. [music] So we hit the long
button then we hope for more. We're
pumping up like the coffee in the cup. J
Casper boy on the treadmill looking
tough. Taking long trades until he says
he has enough. But huh. Do you hear
that? Ruff ruff. The dog. Just kidding.
Not a dog but a bull [music] coming in
to kill the bear in the hole. Haven't
you heard? We go so hard with the
trades. Jay Casper [music] on the
treadmill getting paid. Oh snap. Here we
go. A blue candle. [music] Bitcoin
pumping up. Baby, let me sniff your
sandals. You got the toe cheese. Baby,
please. I'll scrape it out with the
spoon and rub it on my knees. I'll put
it on a bagel. Toe cheese instead of
cream cheese. I'll have you screaming,
"Baby, please don't eat my toe cheese.
It tastes so bad. It's so rotten. It's
the worst I ever had." Uh, we got the
green diddly doot dot on the 24 minute
about to hit the spot. We got the green
diddly duke dot confirmation baby.
Hopefully my trade don't get shot. We
want the green diddly duke dot coming in
on the nice one hour. And if we get the
diddly doo dot, Bitcoin's about to pump
up. Baby, she will have the power.
Chilling out for half an hour. [music]
That's when the candle will close. We
scour the kitchen. We scour the sink. We
got the stainless steel and that's how
we think. We got the stains on the
dishes. Let me eat your Oh, okay. The
beat's over.
All right, the beat's over.
All right, we got the green diddly dot,
baby. We're eating to cheese on the
treadmill. You know, it's come to this,
guys. It has come to this. Eating to
cheese on the treadmill with the green
diddly doo dot. Um,
shout out to Make Me a Millie. He says,
"We got 530 viewers. Do us a favor, fam.
If you haven't already, exit the chat.
Press that and press that thumbs up,
baby, and hop back in." You know what
I'm saying? Hop back in.
Yeah. You think? And what do you guys
think? Do you think we're going to go
come down to the bygon?
Are we going to come down to the bygon?
Are we going to get the bygon setup?
Honestly, if I had to guess based on
this volume profile alone, it looks like
eventually we're going to come down to
the value area low at 627.
But it would not surprise me if we
actually do come down to the bygon. We
have a lot of liquidity down below at
the bygon.
Let's take a poll.
Are we going to come to the bygon?
Do
we come down to the by gone?
Wait, hang on. This keyboard. There we
go. Do we do we come down to the by
gone?
Let by bygones be bygones.
You guys can have your green diddly
dots.
Free Will says lows are not in.
All right. Well, let's see. Let's see. I
have to be honest. This is not looking
good right now. Like, honestly, this is
not looking good. This is not looking
like we're going to continue to the
upside
right here. Okay. So, that's pretty much
what I'm looking at with Bitcoin. If for
some reason we do bounce from here,
[gasps] I mean, honestly,
I don't know. I I I don't know. I don't
know. I could see it going a bunch of
ways. I could see it going like this and
then back down. I could even see it
going like this. Honestly, I could
because of the 1 hour. The 4 hour. If
this thing starts to confirm an oversold
green dot and give us a hidden bullish
divergence and the 1 hour has the green
dot, I could see it going many different
ways right here.
All right. I could see it going many
different ways right here.
What's the bygon gone? It's the big one,
man. It's the big one. Can't you read?
Can't you read
the big one?
Can't you read, man?
Right.
The bygon.
It's the big one. The big trade that
we're waiting for, aka the bygon. All
right.
I do anything till CPI comes out
tomorrow. That's honestly a good way to
go. That's a good way to go.
>> Looks like yesterday. Yeah, seriously.
And yesterday we did get the move up and
then we got a big drop. So, yeah, let's
see what happens. All right, let's check
out some other assets. We'll take a look
at Ethereum here. you know Ethereum in
chop city as well but we are coming down
after forming this range above the PC
this is the range in question we're
holding right now value area low I think
it's pretty important for Ethereum
because ETH is forming this range after
flipping the PC from resistance into
support by the way this is a macro PC
like if we look at the daily time frame
here this is a very very very important
PC it goes all the way back to January
and so if we're going to lose this range
that we formed up here. We could drop
back down into
the previous range. This is the previous
range here. All right. So, very
important that ETH does hold this PC
because if it doesn't, then we could
come back into this range and start
trading in this range again. Right. So,
I would like to see Bitcoin hold
its local range at the bygon and maybe
ETH can hold its local range up here and
then we could see more upside. Let's
check out our weekly on ETH here on
Market Cipher B.
It's still room for the upside. The
two-day o
the 2-day honestly looks like garbageio.
The two-day on ETH really does look like
we're actually going to come back down.
The daily ambiguous. The daily is
looking pretty dang ambiguous.
Man, I'm very curious to see what
happens tomorrow again. Tomorrow at 8:30
in the A.M. All right. This is
approximately 1 hour before New York
open. We have our core CPI coming out.
All right. So, it's interesting. They're
they're actually they're expecting on
the month inflation to go up on the year
inflation to go down.
So, that's interesting. Um,
yeah, they're expecting on the month to
go up, on the on the on the year to go
down.
So, I honestly don't know what that's
going to do to the mortgage, but it is
probably going to have some kind of an
effect here.
I would not be surprised. Oh my
Oh my goodness, guys.
I just got a sinking feeling in the pit
of me a stomach.
I feel like I just lost everything,
guys. One purple candle is all it takes
to wipe out all your gains. One purple
candle is all it takes.
Yeah, I think the bygon is definitely
loading right now.
I think the bygon is definitely loading
right now. Oh my goodness. Lows are 466.
Yeah, I think the low is not in. But uh
I I the local lows can always be in. You
know,
why am I using the log chart for the
bygon? What do you mean?
It's all the same. It's all the same.
Look at this. I'm not using log chart
for the bygon. I'm not using I'm
actually not using log chart for the
bygon.
Was I using log for the bygon? Yeah, I
was. It's about the same.
I don't know. I had it on log by
accident. But either way, this is still
the bygon down here, guys. Whether it's
on log or not log. Whether it's on log
or no log. Okay,
man. Look, I should have taken profit on
it, right? I should have taken profit.
That's the thing. That's the thing. See,
I had the chance. I had one chance, two
chance. Will I get a third chance to
take profit? If I do, do you think I'll
take it? Will I take it or just a
screenshot?
How can it go down on the year if it
goes up on the month? I don't know. I I
don't know. Spicy noodle.
All numbers are cooked.
I mean, the whole economy is cooked kind
of. You know what I'm saying? I'm going
to have to open up a farmers market to
recover from this drop. Absolutely.
Absolutely. Let's see if we can't get a
little bit of a pushup. Let's see if we
can't get a little bit of a push-up
here. We need to do some push-ups. How
many push-ups have you guys done today?
Have you guys done any push-ups today?
Let's see if we get wrecked, man. Let's
see if we get wrecked. Oh my goodness.
Zero push-ups. Not enough push-ups.
Okay, 20 push-ups. That's good. Come on,
Bitcoin. We need a blue candle. We need
to do some push-ups. Negative8 push-ups.
100 push-ups. Wow, that's crazy.
I've probably done about 20 push-ups
today. Maybe more.
All right, memory man moves around a
32ft ladder. That's what's up.
I wasn't supposed to do push-ups today,
but it's really hard not to. It's hard
not to. You know, there's nothing like a
little bit of a chest pump. You know
what I'm saying? In the morning, there's
there's nothing beats a chest pump in
the morning. I I don't know. It's really
hard for me to go more than
>> [laughter]
>> It's really hard for me not to do
push-ups and pull-ups. Just not a lot,
just to get a little bit of a pump, man.
But, you know, speaking of a little bit
of a pump, you know what we really need
right now is a big pump. We need more
than a little bit of a pump. Come on,
Bitcoin.
Let's see if we can't do a little of
this action. Ah,
what was that? Ah, Bitcoin crossing 631
178. It's too late. Oh my goodness. A
massive purple ON THE SIX. WOW. But look
at this.
Oh no. [snorts]
Big shout out to Dennis Marv Jay. Check
who Grant is long. He is waiting at
to shoot Bitcoin to the highs again. I
do pull-ups right now. 50 ines 30 left.
50 and 30 left. All right. Shout out to
Dennis Marv Grant Long. He's waiting for
62K.
Oh, man. Oh, man. That's right where my
stop loss is. Oh, wait. No, my stop loss
a little bit higher than that.
All right. Oh my goodness. This is the
scariest thing I've ever seen in my
life. One giant purple candle to sniff
your sandals.
We're getting cooked.
We're getting cooked. Oh my goodness.
We're getting cooked. Ah, dang it. Ah.
Oh crap. Baby [music] J Casper getting
cooked. Take my eyes off the chart and
then I took a look. Got a giant purple
candle coming down. Sniffing sandals. I
was smiling. Now I got a frown. The
candle is turning back blue. Hopefully
[music and singing] we pump like we want
to do about 30 nice juicy push-ups. Get
a chest pump early in the morning.
Bitcoin dumping down with no warning.
[music] Yeah. Now, here we go. We're in
the house. We're trading Bitcoin. And
we're looking for a juicy Bitcoin
bounce. We were sitting on the couch,
but [music] we felt like a slouch. So,
we got up from the couch. We went to the
gym to get it in the crypto spin. Where
do I begin? Jason in the gym. Crypto
trading. You know, we ain't hating.
We're out here [music] and we're so
frustrated that we always taking losses.
Liquidated again. Have [music] to get
repoed. my Mercedes-Benz cuz I bought
the money. I took a loan but now I got
to go home. We're on the phone. We're
telling a broker we got to sell it all.
Oh my goodness. The candle starts to
fall down the hall. [music] Purple. Oh
man, I can't even handle it. Think
candles handle it.
Lots of shorts. Maybe they get
squizzled. Not going to lie, we need
some to cheese right here, baby. We need
some toe cheese. Let's check out the
market. Uh the uh market monkey.
To cheese. Let's see.
Let's see. Come on. Come on. Come on.
Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come
on.
Come on.
Oh my goodness. Massive amount of shorts
in this wick. Look at that. Yeah. 331
million shorts open in the wick. Maybe
we do squeeze a little bit, man. But
honestly, look at these longs open up.
Look at this bearish CBD that formed
here. Man, I should have been looking at
the chart. Instead, I was rapping about
to cheese. That's what happens, guys.
You think you're good. You think you're
You think you're in profit. You're
rapping about to cheese instead of
looking at Market Monkey Terminal to get
everything right. Sheesh. My goodness.
I know, right? There goes my 36% win
rate. Sheesh.
Um,
where's the stop loss? [laughter]
Oh, the stop loss is is right down here
at uh
63250. I I figure I give a little bit of
playing room here in case in case we do
this in case we do this and then come
back in and form a nice bottom, right?
So, that's what I'm looking at here. And
if not, then I I guess value area low is
next,
you know. If not, then I suppose value
area low is next.
Send it straight to the Van Allen
radiation belts, baby.
Do I like dachshunds? I do love
dachshunds. I think they're I think
they're cute little pups. All right. I'm
more of a beagle guy, but dachshunds are
like long, short, weeny drag on the
ground beagles. But here's the thing. I
had a beagle when I was a kid.
And he was so fat that his weenie
actually did drag on the floor. He was
so fat. You should have seen this
beagle. He was so fat. I mean, we would
feed him white castles and slices of
pizza. Maybe one time he ate a whole
stick of butter. I felt bad for the
beagle. I'll tell you what, he loved
food. This dude lived to eat. This
beagle, he lived to eat. So me and him,
we were on the same brain wave in that
aspect. We love to eat. You know, go to
White Castle, get a few crave cases of
cheeseburgers, and split it with your
dog.
Um, but yeah, let me tell you, his
weenie dragged on the floor. All right,
that's how fat he was.
Um,
man, this this sucks though. This does
suck. This looks like garbage.
It looks like garbage.
It looks like garbage. Garbagino.
Dang it, man. So much for trying to look
like a hero on the internet. Long in the
bottom. Look, everyone has fun and games
long in the bottom until it's no longer
the bottom. [laughter]
I long the exact bottom 17 times today.
Do I think we're coming down to take low
at 62 230? Yeah, we might. We might. We
might. We might. Want to feel weird? I
converted your Billy videos to MP3s. Now
you listen right before you go to sleep.
That's a little weird, man.
That's a little weird to think about.
some some some person listening to my
voice before they go to sleep. That's a
little bit strange. All right, can we
check XRP? As soon as this trade is
either stopped out or in the green, I
can check XRP. But right now, I just
can't handle it.
I just can't handle watching this this
pain and misery on the chart,
you know? I just can't handle I just
can't handle it, man. You know what
[music] I mean?
Oh, it is tough. It is tough. What can I
say?
Oh my goodness. You know, this is some
pretty big pain in misery. We're making
a new low as I speak. We're in the We're
in the We're in the Rojo $1,000. Oh my
goodness. Oh my goodness.
Oh.
Ah.
All right. Let's see what's going to
happen here.
Let's put on our stop loss on the chart
so everyone can watch it happen. We'll
watch it happen together.
What the heck?
I got to refresh.
Is my stop loss here? My stop loss
better be here, right? Is it here?
What?
Wait, what the heck?
Wait,
wait. Are we First of all, what happened
to my stop loss? And second of all,
Wait, what the heck just happened here?
What?
Wait a second. Wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait a second. Wait a second. Wait a
second.
Wait a second.
What? Wait, wait, wait, wait.
What is going on right now?
Guys, I'm Am I [__]
What the heck is going on right now?
What is actually happening right now?
What the heck has just happened here? Do
How am I down $1,000 realized profit and
in a long trade from lower? Did I like
add to my position by accident just now?
Like, what the heck?
Wait,
wait a second.
I'm legitimately confused right now,
guys.
What? [laughter] What the heck? What the
heck?
All right, this was my trade.
It it it it it was a market order. It
got stopped out. This was my stop loss.
So why am I in another trade right now
for $324,000?
Am I [__] What? What the heck is
going on, man? This is the
Yeah. Was it a limit order? Was it a
limit order?
Was it a limit order? That's what I'm
trying to find. Where's my order
history?
I just see market orders only.
Oh, [groaning]
okay.
Okay. It was a limit order. [music] It
was a limit order at 63250.
Okay. All right. It was a limit order.
So, I got stopped out and I had a limit
order that I forgot about. Huh.
Huh.
Okay. All right. That was weird, guys.
All right. Man, that was the weirdest
thing. [laughter]
All right. Well, all right. Oh my
goodness. What the actual man?
[laughter]
Oh my goodness.
All right. Oh god. Okay. All right.
Okay. Okay. Just a little bit. Re just a
little bit. Re Okay. Yeah. Shout out to
Bad Boy. He knows what's happening here.
Oh man, that was so funny.
A free solo. That's why I started
exercising again because I had fat
fingers.
All right. Okay. Okay. I see. I see. I
see what happened here. All right. I see
what happened here. Man, I thought I was
losing it, guys. I thought I was
legitimately losing it.
You know, I thought I was legitimately
losing it.
Yeah, looks like we're still going to
come lower, though. Let's see.
We'll put our stop loss up here. We
won't want to risk too much on that one.
What a strange turn of events, guys.
Honestly, what a strange strange turn of
events. What's up with this though?
1,119.
Is that like slippage? I've never had
that happen to me on AX before. Not like
that. What the heck?
That sucks.
Yeah,
we got a crack in the matrix, baby.
Yeah, that can't be fees. I don't know
what that is. I It might be slippage or
something. I have no idea. That's really
strange. This whole thing has been very
strange. I I I'll be honest with you.
I'm I'm a little bit freaked out in
[music] the moment here with all this
stuff that's just happened to me. You
know,
you walked away, Crypto Crank. Did I
re-enter? Go back and watch the stream a
little bit, bro. Cuz cuz I had the most
strange thing happen to me in my life,
man. I literally had the strangest thing
happened to me ever, which was I was
trying to get my stop loss to show up on
the chart. I refreshed the
the screen and something crazy happened
and it turns out I had a limit order set
that I forgot about. So, I did get this
limit order filled and so I guess I'm
long again, bro. Uh, let's see what
happens now. Let's see. I I ended up
taking a loss on that one.
So,
it's not the best thing in the world to
be honest.
might be time to sell the tractor now.
Yeah, seriously.
I just market sold the position to
myself. I guess you're right.
Frictionism.
Yeah, I guess you're right. Sheesh, man.
Well, that's why I always say this ain't
no financial advice, guys. I'm just an
idiot on the treadmill.
Just an idiot on the treadmill.
Can you imagine if we pump from here,
baby?
Can you imagine if we pump from here?
What do you guys You guys feeling the
pump coming on? You guys feeling a pump
coming on? I'm feeling a pump coming on.
Oh man, I'm feeling a pump coming on
right now.
I'm feeling a pump coming on right now.
Here we go, baby. Talk about a knife
catch.
>> [music]
>> Here we go, baby.
We're about to pop
the Bitcoin price back to back test the
support resistance limit at least right
here. Let's see [music] if we can't have
this level. We'll do it with the power
of music.
Here we go.
Let's go. Here we go, baby. [music]
Yeah.
[music]
Here we go, baby.
We going to dump.
No, we're going to pop. We're going to
dump. [music]
Heat. Heat.
[music]
Here [music]
we go.
Let's go. Let's go. [music]
Let's go.
Here we go, baby.
It's working a little bit.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Yeah.
Try to $100,000.
$100,000.
Yeah.
Here
we go. [music]
Yeah. Here we go.
Here we go. Here we go. Here we go.
Wow. [screaming]
[music]
Heat.
Yeah.
[music]
It's working, baby.
It is working, baby. Here we go. Man,
this is some old school Jason Casper
playlist right here. This is the the
synth wave journey. Remember this?
Yeah, I remember this.
Yeah, it takes me back. the the these
these songs take me back.
You know,
I don't think we're going to get very
much from this, guys. I'll be honest.
I just felt like singing the pump song
into a rubber chicken. I'll be honest.
I just I just felt like singing the pump
song into a rubber chicken. That's all.
So, so let's see what happens here. Oh,
man. Close the along to a dumb song.
Yeah, I don't know,
man. I I mean,
let's see. Let's let's let's You know
what? When in doubt, let's take a look
at good old market cipher beat. 6 minute
decent. Man, can you believe that that
24-minute diddly doo dot failed us here?
But there is a chance this turns into
another div. I mean, it's it's really
not looking good, guys. I If I had to
give a goose a gander, then we're coming
back down to this is the next level down
here. If I had to give the goose a
gander, if I had to give the goose a
gander, going to give the goose a
gander.
I'd say I'd say we're coming down to
that level. You know what? Sometimes you
got to look at the chart through a
different lens.
Let's take a look here.
Mhm. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes.
Yes. Yes. I I I do think we probably
come lower.
No. And in hindsight, after singing the
pump song, I do believe we may come
lower.
It's okay to give the goose a gander,
but never give the goose a gobbler.
Okay.
Why have I raised profit if it's a new
limit order? That's That's what I don't
quite understand. It must be some kind
of a fee here. Let's check it out.
So if that was this limit ordered right
here,
trading fee zero. So it must be slippage
or something or someone else. Is it? I
don't know. I honestly I don't know,
man.
I do not know. I do not know. I do not
know.
I don't know.
I don't know. I've never quite had
anything like this happen to me before.
I mean, I've had limit orders that I
forgot about. It's just so weird the
sequence of events, the stop loss being
hit. I could the only thing I can think
of is that this is a combination of my
last position and my current position.
Maybe cuz my stop loss was exactly on my
limit order cuz I had the the stop loss
at 63250
and apparently the limit order was also
at 63250 and I totally forgot about
that. So I think because the limit order
and the stop loss were in the same
place, something strange happened here.
That's the only thing I can possibly
think.
You know,
maybe the position didn't fully close.
Yeah. I mean, I don't know. I don't
know. I've never had anything like this
happen before.
No, it was not a limit stop loss.
It automatically closes it after 8 hours
and opens a new trade with the same
position.
What? No, it doesn't.
Yeah, I don't know.
I could speculate forever. The only
thing I really want to do now is I want
to see if we can reclaim the yellow line
and Maybe we could maybe we could get
some pump action here, but I don't know.
Let's check out the order flow again. We
do still have a lot of shorts that
opened up here. 451 415 million shorts
on this candle. So, we do start to
reclaim this and we could see a little
bit of a squealle. Although, you know
what's crazy? These longs here, guys,
are also still open. So, all these guys
are still open. So, this is actually all
these longs here are [music] are
probably fuel for more downside. The
fact that pretty much everybody that
longed in here is still open, I guess,
including me, that makes me think we we
definitely not definitely, but we're
probably going to come down to the value
area low.
You know, I wouldn't consider this
bullish CBD. Uh, whoever asked that, no,
I would not consider this bullish CBD.
I would consider this in some ways
bearish because mostly we have many
longs opened in this area here and
they're still open and they're all
underwater. So we have a few shorts
underwater but mostly longs. So let's
see what happens. I mean if if we start
to squeeze the shorts in this candle and
we have more buyers step in, we could
get the move to the upside, you know.
Let's see what's going to happen here.
Come on, Bitcoin.
Come on.
Oh. Oh, okay. I think I know what
happened. It's still the same position
and it stopped out some of the position
and not all the position. That's
probably what happened. That's probably
what happened, right? I don't know.
Something happened.
It makes sense. There's all these
speculations in the chat. Something
happened. It'll all work out. It'll all
work out. Juicy squeeze coming, says Z
Valdi. The question is, is a squeeze
going to go up or down?
Got to be crazy to buy right now with
the news. That's Are we're talking about
buying Bitcoin on spot? Cuz honestly, if
when there's bearish news, that's
exactly when you want to be buying
Bitcoin on spot. But
when was the last time I did the pump
song? Just a few minutes ago, man. Just
a few minutes ago.
Just a few minutes ago.
This is a slow, painful action today,
man. I'll tell you.
It closed and filled, says Crypto Crank.
Well, I closed a $400,000 position and
opened a $324,000
position somehow. So, it was a little
bit different,
but I'm not sure, man. I don't know.
If you waited for the news, you would
never be able to trade. Yeah, seriously.
Po show po.
Why is Monero banned on every exchange?
It's a privacy coin. It's
that's the thing about Monero is, you
know, it's valuable because you're
supposed to use it secretly. So, you
can't really use it secretly on an
exchange.
And a lot of a lot of governments don't
like Monero. They view it as dangerous
because it's anonymous.
It's a real privacy coin. I need a slice
of pepperoni and cheese. Yeah, me too. I
need that as well. I really do.
All right. I I have to I have to pee,
guys. I'll be right back. I'm going to
pee out the window. I'll take you guys
with me. Let's Let's all pee out the
window together. All right. Let's all
pee out the window together.
We will pee.
Come with me and we'll pee.
in this world of crazy looking window.
Is that not the craziest thing you've
ever seen in your life out there, guys?
Oh man,
nothing like peeing out the window. Look
at that beautiful window.
That beautiful place out there just to
pee. Just let it all
I'm eating a soft pretzel, says New
York, New Earth Guardian. You're eating
a soft pretzel, are you?
That's cool.
I love soft pretzels. Oh, man.
You know, back in the day before I was a
healthy eater, probably every single
night,
every single night, I would have a beer,
two or three soft pretzels,
and some popcorn chicken, like breaded
chicken that I made in the toaster oven.
And that was like my bedtime snack.
That was back in my 20s, let me tell you
guys.
I don't miss that at all.
Nothing like peeing with the brothers.
Just peed in a yellow jacket nest. You
know what's funny is, you know what?
There are actually still old dead yellow
jackets in here because do you guys
remember when my when my office was
infested with yellow jackets the other
day?
Wait, don't pee. That's not a real
window. Yeah, here's the thing. The
yellow jackets. Let's see if you guys
can see there. Their dead bodies are
still strewn all over the uh
Yeah, let's see if you guys can see
these yellow jacket bodies in here. I
don't know if you can see them in the
window crack there. Those yellow jacket
bodies. Man, I had an infestation of
yellow jackets. Let me tell you, it was
crazy. You know, I was live streaming,
killing these yellow jackets with the
plunger. You guys remember that? The OGs
will remember that, you know.
Wow. Wow. What a cool office. What a
cool office we got here. What a cool
desk. Wow. Wow. Look at that behind the
scenes. Breaking the fourth wall with
Jason Casper. Breaking the fourth wall
with Jason Casper.
Let it flow. Tony Braxton. Pjam. Any
ideas on XRP? Yeah,
we should take a look at XRP. Oh man,
the ants pretzels. You know what? Not
not quicker. I never really like those
cuz I I never liked my pretzels full of
butter, you know? I never liked them the
way the antie made them buttery. I like
them dry. I like the uh the the super
pretzel kind that that are in that giant
thing that spins around on the hooks,
you know, at like football games and
stuff. That's the kind I liked. So, I
used to buy the New York style ones and
bake them in the oven. That was the way
I did it, man.
This was the way I did it. All right, we
could take a little look at XRP here.
All right, let's take a little look at
XRP.
Come with me and we'll be in a land of
pure urination,
man. Yeah, that that infestation was
months ago. It was so long ago. That was
before I went to Cuba. I'm going back to
Cuba, guys.
I'm going back to Cuba.
Is this a real song?
Let's see before we look at XRP. Man,
we're about to get wrecked again.
Okay, I don't think I could I don't
think I could actually like freestyle to
that. All right, let's let's put on some
some boom bat 90s music. All right, boom
back 90s. And let's take a look at XRP.
Looks like we want to come down to the
circle here. XRP
USDT.
All right, let's take a look at XRP.
Man, I wish XRPs I wish Bitcoin was
doing what what XRP is doing. Look at
that on the day, man. XRP getting a
bounce.
Um, so we took the lows.
Actually, the the daily looks kind of
nice on at least like
at the 786. We're getting a a little bit
of a liquidity grab, but
um
obviously a nicer level. All the all the
lower levels would be nicer.
Or just take a look at this. I I don't I
don't really have too many thoughts on
XRP
in the sense that would I buy XRP now? I
I would not personally. I don't plan to
buy XRP by the way, but I would rather
wait for something juicier than this or
some kind of change of market structure
or sign of strength cuz right now there
is no sign of strength. We're grinding
to the downside. So, it literally is
trying to catch knife in the sense that
like if we're buying on spot, we don't
even have any kind of weekly structure
change or anything, but we still have
pretty much no support below us. Like,
we could easily come back down to 71
if there's like a big move down. If
Bitcoin does make a new low, you know,
but if you're trying to build an XRP
position,
anything 73% lower, I mean, that's
objectively speaking a good deal, right?
So, if you're going to try and build a
position, ain't nothing wrong with
starting after a 73% dip. If we come
down more, I mean, you could build
yourself a juicy position in this area,
and obviously
I'm of I'm in the opinion that XRP is
still going to pump in the future. Okay?
Everyone has their own opinions on it.
You know what I'm saying? Whoa, big
shout out to the super chat.
Is my ultimate plan to move to Cuba?
I don't know. Shout out to uh 20 2025
resurrection. Keep peing out the window.
Feeling like a king. Yellow rain
falling. Hear the neighbor scream. No
toilet needed. We free the beast. Window
open wide. Let it flow east.
Uh uh. Okay. Those are some nice bars.
They are some nice bars.
Hey yo. Uh. Hey yo, [music] peeing out
the window, feeling like a king. Yellow
rain falling. Hear the neighbors scream.
No toilet needed. We free the beast.
Window open wide. Let it flow east,
baby. Peing out the window, feeling like
a king.
Thank you so much for the super chat. I
appreciate that. I appreciate that. The
super chat.
Oh, is shout out to Dave Digital. God
bless you, bro. Is Divine Hood
streaming? Let's check it. Let's check
it out. Divine Hood.
Divine Hood. Is he live now?
>> All right, guys.
>> Let's go raid. Let's go raid right now.
>> Divine Hood stream.
>> Let's all head over to Divine Hood
stream right now. In fact, let's end
this stream right now.